Dunya Ramicova Costume Design Collection MSS.004
University of California, Merced Library
- Production Materials, Ephemera, and Process Notes, 66 Boxes
  - Box 134
    - The Magic Flute - Character Design Process Notes (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - The Magic Flute - Production Correspondence (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - The Magic Flute - Costume Production Reference (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - The Magic Flute - Costume Production Reference (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - The Magic Flute - Playbill (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - The Magic Flute - Reviews (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Box 135
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1988) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1988) - Costume Plot and Scene Breakdown (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1988) - Production (Rehearsal) Reports (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1988) - Pre-production Publicity (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1988) - Playbill (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1989) - Cast List (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1989) - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Costume Lists, Photographs from Final Fittings, and Fabric Swatches (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1989) - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Costume Lists, Photographs from Final Fittings, and Fabric Swatches (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1989) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Preset List and Costume Change Plot (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - The Marriage of Figaro (1989) - Reviews (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Box 136
    - The Voyage - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with David Pountney, Robert Israel, Quinny Sacks, and Gil Wechsler (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - The Voyage - Pictorial Research (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - The Voyage - Pictorial Research (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - The Voyage - Costume Production Reference (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Box 137
    - The Voyage - Costume Production Reference (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - The Voyage - Costume Production Reference (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - The Voyage - Production Faxes (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - The Voyage - Pre-opening Publicity (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - The Voyage - Playbills (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - The Voyage - Reviews (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Box 138
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Synopsis and Libretto (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Written Research Notes (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Process Drawings of Narrator's Circles (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Color Palette Notes (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Costume Production Reference (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Costume Production Reference (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Playbill (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - The Gospel According to the Other Mary - Reviews (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Box 139
    Miscellaneous playbills for productions with costume designs by Dunya Ramicova.
    - The Cherry Orchard, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Passions, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - The Tiller in the Fields, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - The Memorandum (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - The Thirteen Clocks, ND (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - The Snow Queen, 1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Two Plays by Samuel Beckett, ND (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - A Macbeth, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Salonika, ND (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Bosoms and Neglect, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Candida, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Curse of the Starving Class, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - On the Verge, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Charley's Aunt, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Who's Life is it Anyway, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Cyrano de Bergerac, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - The Front Page, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Box 140
    Oversized playbills for productions featuring costume designs by Dunya Ramicova. Included are playbills for the following productions: The Duchess of Malfi (ND); Tales from the Vienna Woods / Mistaken Identities / Mahogany (1978); The Vietnamization of New Jersey / The Durango Flash / Mister Puntilla and His Chauffer Matti (1977); Buried Child / The Seagull / The Bundle / As You Like It (1979); The Ghost Sonata / Reunion / Terra Nova (1977); Sganarelle / Man is Man / Wings / The Wild Duck (1978); Cosi fan Tutti (1996); Theodora (2003); White Marriage / Puntilla (1977); His Bartholomew Faire (ND).
  - Box 141
    Miscellaneous oversized playbills and publications.
  - Box 142
    Miscellaneous playbills and publications.
- Production Scripts, 5 Boxes
  - Box 143
    - Nixon in China (1 of 2), M1503.A32 N59 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Nixon in China (2 of 2), M1503.A32 N59 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - I Was Looking at the Ceiling and Then I Saw the Sky, ML50.A33 14 1994 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - An American Tragedy, ML50.P553 A64 2003a (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - An American Tragedy, ML50.P553 A64 2003a (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - An American Tragedy, ML50.P553 A64 2003b (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - An American Tragedy, ML50.P553 A64 2004 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Platonov, PG3456.P43 1977 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Three Sisters, PG3456.T57 1984 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - The Master and Margarita, PG3476.B78 M313 1978 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Box 144
    - Temptation, PG5038.H3 T46 1989 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Largo Desolato, PG5039.18.A9 L3713 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Hester on the Scaffold, PN611.H3 S33 1997 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - The Possessed, PN611.K38 P677 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - The Triumph of Love, PQ2003.T7513 1988 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Windows (1 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Windows (2 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Windows (3 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Windows (4 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Windows (5 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Windows (6 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Windows (7 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Box 145
    - Windows (8 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Windows (9 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Windows (10 of 10), PQ8098.4.O7 V513 1991 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Fanshen, PR6058.A678 F3 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Melons, PR6066.O48 W4 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Pride and Prejudice, PR6066.O995 P7 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - The Lady in the Labyrinth, PR643.M7 L339 1988 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Hedda Gabler, PS3552.A393 H44 1999 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Stickers and Starlight Talkers, PS3552.E82 S85 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake, PS3552.L43 C48 1998 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Chopin in Space, PS3552.O783 C46 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Box 146
    - No Mercy, PS3553.O48779 N6 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Grown Ups, PS3556.E42 G7 1981 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Ceremony in Bohemia, PS3556.O721 C47 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - 313 West End Ave, PS3559.A7254 H38 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Rococo, PS3561.O456 R62 1980 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Search and Destroy, PS3561.O6567 S4 1988 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - The Trial of One Short-Sighted Black Woman vs. Mammy Louise and Safreeta Mae, PS3562.E827 T75 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - F.M., PS3562.I51169 F6 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Something About Baseball, PS3562.O4946 S64 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Box 147
    - Faulkner's Bicycle, PS3563.C3565 F38 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Kafka's Radio, PS3565.V432 A19 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - The Resurrection of Lady Lester, PS3565.Y3 R47 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Emmeline, PS3568.O848 E4 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Hang on to Me, PS3569.E55 H35 1984 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez, PS3569.E55 L32 1989 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - The Memento, PS3575.A447 M46 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - The School for Scandal, PS3682.S3 1986 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Workin' for Peanuts, PZ7.S899 W6 1984 (Box 147, Folder 9)